<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-04-06T23:28:34+02:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">GMod: Containment Breach</title><entry><title type="html">Update 1</title><link href="/2021/04/06/update1/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Update 1" /><published>2021-04-06T20:56:05+02:00</published><updated>2021-04-06T20:56:05+02:00</updated><id>/2021/04/06/update1</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/04/06/update1/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;new-website--blog&quot;&gt;New Website &amp;amp; Blog&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve set up this temporary website, that will serve as a place for me to write these update blogs.
As you can see it’s still very barebones, but i will slowly start giving this site a proper look.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will eventually move this away from Github Pages, but for now this will be fine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;player-controlled-scps&quot;&gt;Player controlled SCPs&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been thinking about how SCP NPCs will work in terms of research, and i’ve come to the conclusion that it is not worth the effort to make this work, nor do i think it’s feasible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So instead SCPs will be controlled by Game Masters, which will cut down Development time of this gamemode by a lot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This will also make the roleplay interaction between players and SCPs a lot better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;alpha-testing&quot;&gt;Alpha Testing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently there are no Alpha testing sessions going on, however i plan to change this as i introduce more SCPs and features.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will most likely rent out a small server, which will enable me to host testing sessions much easier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;discord-advertising&quot;&gt;Discord Advertising&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I haven’t been paying much attention to the discord so far, but i plan to change that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not entirely sure what i will do about this yet, but i’ll try to come up with something.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">New Website &amp;amp; Blog</summary></entry></feed>